Julián Guillermo Agüero

Phone: +34-644092723 | Email: julianaguero@gmail.com | Madrid, Spain. 28028

Linkedin.com/julianaguero

Github.com/julianaguero

Front-end developer with over 3 years of experience in recruiting, seeking a challenging position in a dynamic company where I can leverage my technical and communication skills.

ABOUT ME

Professional with over 3 years of experience in management and recruiting, and a passion for web development. With a solid background in this field, I have developed exceptional interpersonal, communication, leadership, teamwork, and third-party providers management skills. Seeking a position as web developer to capitalize on experience with JavaScript, React, Next.js, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, and PostgreSQL. I bring a strong sense of commitment, dedication, and adaptability to every project I undertake. Passionate about using technology as a driver of success in any sector, I firmly believe in continuous improvement.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RUN THE CODE | Full-Stack Developer | 2023

- Led a 3-member team responsible for the design, layout, and front-end development of a website, proposing the implementation of agile methodologies as a work strategy.
- Developed and **implemented the backend** for products with a MySQL database, including controllers and routes, for an e-commerce platform.
- Technologies used: JavaScript, React, Python, MySQL.

Car Hub | Full-Stack Developer | 2023

- Developed a Next.js application, consuming data from two different APIs, including integrated pagination, filtering, and search functionality.
- -Technologies used: Next.js, Tailwind CSS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mr. Cabeza Lapiz | Front End Developer | June 2023 - current

- MERN Stack: JavaScript (ES6), MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js

ECC SL - Madrid | Head Manager | July 2022 - April 2023

- Led a six-member team, provided mentoring, contributing to the professional improvement of the group.
- Optimized tasks and resources within my area, streamlining production processes and improving execution times.

DET VIDE HUS - Copenhaguen | Team Manager | March 2019 - April 2020

- Conducted staff training and performance evaluations.
- Participated in the design, management, and development of new projects under my supervision.
- Worked with a multicultural team, contributing to improving group dynamics and communication.

Grupo GEA - Healthcare Companies - Córdoba, Arg. | HH.RR. | October 2013 - December 2018

- Participated in the selection and hiring of personnel, leveraging my experience in psychology and team management.
- Headed an internal project focused on improving worker productivity, providing mentoring, and implementing a new access system and overall data structure.

SKILLS

Fast learner | Strategic planning | Teamwork | Inclusive leadership | Abstract thinking | Adaptability | Problem-solving | Pragmatic thinking | Project management | Team leadership | HTML | Tailwind CSS | JavaScript | React | Vue.js | Next.js | Node.js | Express | MySQL | SQLite | Git | Mongo.DB | PostgreSQL

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer | Codo a Codo 4.0 | February 2023 - July 2023

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, MongoDB (900+ hs coding)

Database Developer with SQL, Data Modeling, and Data Storage/Database Administration. | Udemy | February 2023

Big Data Architecture | Formate | October 2022 - January 2023

Bachelor's degree in Psychology | Universidad Nacional de Córdoba | March 2012 - July 2018

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Native. - English: Proficient.